NATTHAWADEE CHANSIRINUKROH

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



- **2** 080-264-4333
- bobow.kj@gmail.com
- Phasicharoen, Bangkok
- github.com/bobow22

PROFILE

I am currently learning to be a full-stack developer. Experiences in both the art and business fields help me improve my creative and analytical skills significantly, and I want to challenge myself to further steps in programming which I can use my potential to build great applications

SKILLS

- HTML & CSS
- Node JS
- Javascript
- Express JS
- React
- SOL
- Bootstrap
- Chart JS
- Antd
- Tailwind
- C
- Adobe Photoshop
- Figma
- Organized
- TOEIC 900
- Detailed-oriented
- Digital
- Collarborative
- Painting
- Hardworking

EXPERIENCE

RETAIL EXECUTION EXECUTIVE

Colgate-Palmolive (Thailand) Limited 2018 - 2019

- Maintain pricing in SAP
- Execute point of purchase for department stores
- Administer Purveyance (CRM Tools)

DATA ANALYST

T.G. Cellular World Company Limited 2018

Create Sales analysis report and data visualizations

FREELANCE ILLUSTRATOR

2016 - 2017

• Make an illustration based on a concept that a customer provides.

FREELANCE TUTOR

2015

• Teach Math and English to primary school students

EDUCATION

DEVCAMP 2022

Full-stack javascript web developer Internship at FlowAccount

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

Assumption University

2010 - 2014

Major: Business Information System

Concentration: Accounting

REFERENCE

PAIBOON PANUSBORDEE

President of Thai Programmer Association

Tel. 082 356 9495

Email: paiboon@thaiprogrammer.org